<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.atelier.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license> GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Atölye</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxAtelierxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Atelier</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Atelier</name>
  <summary> 3D Printer Host </summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Amfitrió d'impressora en 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Amfitrió d'impressora en 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Nástroj na ovládání 3D tiskárny</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Vært til 3D-printer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Υπολογιστής για 3D εκτυπωτή</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">3D Printer Host</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Servidor de impresión 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">3D printimine</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">3D inprimagailu ostalaria</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">3D-tulostuspalvelin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Hôte d'imprimante pour imprimantes 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Máquina de impresora 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Host Printer 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Host di stampa 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">3D 프린터 호스트</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">3D-printerhost</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">3D-skrivarvert</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Gospodarz drukarek 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Assistente de Impressoras 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Gazdă pentru imprimantă 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Hostiteľ 3D tlače</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Gostitelj 3D tiskalnika</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Skrivarvärd för tredimensionella skrivare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">3B Yazıcı Denetleyici</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Вузол для тривимірного друку</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xx3D Printer Hostxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">3D Printer Host</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">3D 列印主機</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Atelier allows you to connect to and control a 3D printer from your computer. You can control any number of printers and open any number of files. Aside from printing, you can preview the gcodes, view an attached camera, edit your files, and manage your machine(s). </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'Atelier permet connectar i controlar una impressora en 3D des de l'ordinador. Podreu controlar qualsevol nombre d'impressores i obrir qualsevol nombre de fitxers. A part de la impressió, podreu previsualitzar els gcodes, veure una càmera adjunta, editar els vostres fitxers i gestionar la/es màquina/es.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Atelier permet connectar i controlar una impressora en 3D des de l'ordinador. Podreu controlar qualsevol nombre d'impressores i obrir qualsevol nombre de fichers. A part de la impressió, podreu previsualisar els gcodes, vore una càmara adjunta, editar els vostres fichers i gestionar les màquines.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Atelier lader dig tilslutte og kontrollere en 3D-printer fra din computer. Du kan kontrollere et ubegrænset antal printere og åbne et ubegrænset antal filer. Udover at printe kan du forhåndsvise gcodes, se et tilsluttet kamera, redigere dine filer og håndtere dine maskiner.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Atelier σάς επιτρέπει να συνδεθείτε και να ελέγξετε έναν 3D εκτυπωτή από τον υπολογιστή σας. Μπορείτε να ελέγχετε οποιονδήποτε αριθμό εκτυπωτών και να ανοίξετε οποιοδήποτε πλήθος αρχείων. Εκτός των εκτυπώσεων, μπορείτε να κάνετε προεπισκόπηση των gcode, να προβάλλετε μια εγκατεστημένη κάμερα, να επεξεργαστείτε τα αρχεία σας και να διαχειριστείτε τις συσκευές σας.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Atelier allows you to connect to and control a 3D printer from your computer. You can control any number of printers and open any number of files. Aside from printing, you can preview the gcodes, view an attached camera, edit your files, and manage your machine(s).</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Atelier le permite conectarse y controlar una impresora 3D desde su equipo. Puede controlar cualquier número de impresoras y abrir cualquier número de archivos. Además de imprimir, puede previsualizar los gcodes, ver una cámara emparejada, editar sus archivos y administrar sus máquinas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Atelier võimaldab otse arvutist ühendada 3D printeri ja seda juhtida. Võimalik on juhtida piiramatul arvul printereid ja avada nii palju faile, kui tarvis. Lisaks trükkimisele saab näha G-koodi eelvaatlust ja uurida ühendatud kaamerat, muuta faile ning hallata masinaid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Atelier-rek 3D inprimagailuetara konektatu eta haiek kontrolatzeko aukera ematen dizu. Edozein inprimagailu kopuru kontrolatu eta edozein fitxategi kopuru ireki dezakezu. Inprimatzeaz gain, G-kode fitxategiak aurreikusi, atxikitako kamera batetik ikusi, zure fitxategiak editatu, eta zure makinak kudeatu ditzakezu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Atelier’lla voit yhdistää tietokoneelta 3D-tulostimeen ja hallita sitä. Tulostinten ja avointen tiedostojen määrää ei ole rajoitettu. Tulostamisen lisäksi voit esikatsella gcodeja, nähdä liitetyn kameran, muokata tiedostoja ja hallita konetta.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le programme Atelier vous permet de vous connecter et de contrôler une imprimante 3D à partir de votre ordinateur. Vous pouvez contrôler n'importe quel nombre d'imprimantes et ouvrir n'importe quel nombre de fichiers. En plus de l'impression, vous pouvez afficher un aperçu des « gcodes », afficher l'image d'une caméra embarquée, modifier vos fichiers et gérer vos machines.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Atelier permítelle conectar o computador a impresoras 3D e controlalas. Pode controlar tantas impresoras e abrir tanto ficheiros como queira. Ademais de imprimir pode obter unha vista previa do código G, ver a cámara conectada, editar os ficheiros e xestionar as máquinas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Atelier memungkinkan kamu untuk terkoneksi dan mengendalikan printer 3D dari komputermu. Kamu bisa mengendalikan sejumlah printer dan membuka sejumlah file. Selain mencetak, kamu bisa melihat pratinjau gcode, menampilkan kamera yang terpasang, mengedit file-mu, dan mengelola mesinmu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Atelier ti permette di connettere la tua stampante 3D al computer e di controllarla per mezzo di esso. Puoi controllare un qualsiasi numero di stampanti ed aprire tutti i file che vuoi. Oltre alla stampa puoi fare un'anteprima del codice G, visualizzare una fotocamera collegata, modificare i file e gestire le tue macchine.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Atelier를 사용하여 컴퓨터에 연결된 3D 프린터를 제어할 수 있습니다. 임의의 프린터와 파일을 동시에 제어할 수 있습니다. 인쇄 작업 이외에도 G 코드 미리 보기, 연결된 카메라 미리 보기, 파일 편집, 머신 관리를 지원합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Atelier stelt u in staat om te verbinden met een 3D-printer en deze te besturen vanaf uw computer. U kunt elk aantal printers besturen en elke aantal bestanden openen. Naast printen, kunt u de gcodes bekijken een aangekoppelde camera bekijken, uw bestanden bewerken en uw machine(s) beheren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Atelier lèg deg kopla til og styra 3D-skrivarar frå datamaskina. Det finst inga grense på talet på skrivarar du kan styra eller filer du kan opna. I tillegg til 3D-skriving kan du førehandsvisa G-kodar, bruka tilkopla kamera, redigera filer og setja opp maskinene.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Atelier umożliwia podłączenie i sterowanie drukarką 3D z komputera. Można sterować dowolną licz”ą drukarek i otworzyć dowolną liczbę plików. Poza drukowaniem, można przeglądać pliki gcode, obejrzeć załączony aparat, edytować pliki i zarządzać maszyną.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Atelier permite-lhe contactar e controlar uma impressora 3D a partir do seu computador. Poderá controlar um número qualquer de impressoras e abrir uma quantidade qualquer de ficheiros. Para além de imprimir, poderá antever os 'gcodes', ver uma câmara ligada, editar os seus ficheiros e gerir as suas máquinas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Atelier vám umožní pripojiť a ovládať 3D tlačiareň z vášho počítača. Môžete ovládať ľubovoľný počet tlačiarní a súborov. Okrem tlače si môžete prezerať gcodes, pripojené kamery, upravovať vaše súbory a spravovať vaše stroje.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Atelier vam omogoča povezavo in upravljanje 3D-tiskalnika s svojega računalnika. Nadzorujete lahko poljubno število tiskalnikov in odprete poljubno število datotek. Poleg tiskanja si lahko predhodno ogledate gcode, imate pogled skozi priloženo kamero, urejate datoteke in upravljate z vašimi stroji.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Atelier gör det möjligt att ansluta till och styra en tredimensionell skrivare från datorn. Det går att styra hur många skrivare som helst och öppna hur många filer som helst. Förutom utskrift kan man förhandsgranska Gcode, visa en ansluten kamera, redigera filer och hantera maskiner.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Atölye, bilgisayarınıza bir 3B yazıcı bağlamanıza ve onu denetlemenize izin verir. İstediğiniz sayıda yazıcı bağlayabilir ve istediğiniz sayıda dosya yazdırabilirsiniz. Yazdırmadan başka, gcodes'ları önizleyebilir, ilişik bir kamerayı görüntüleyibilir, dosyalarınızı düzenleyebilir ve makinelerinizi yönetebilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою Atelier ви зможете встановити з'єднання між вашим тривимірним принтером та комп'ютером та керувати принтером. Передбачено керування довільною кількістю принтерів та відкриття довільної кількості файлів. Окрім друку, ви можете переглядати код gcode, переглядати зображення із приєднаної камери, редагувати файли та керувати вашими машинами.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAtelier allows you to connect to and control a 3D printer from your computer. You can control any number of printers and open any number of files. Aside from printing, you can preview the gcodes, view an attached camera, edit your files, and manage your machine(s).xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Atelier 允许您在计算机上连接并控制 3D 打印机。 您可以控制任意数量的打印机并打开任意数量的文件。 除了打印以外，您可以预览 gcodes，查看连接的相机，编辑您的文件，并管理您的机器。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Atelier 讓您可以從您的電腦連線並控制 3D 印表機。您可以控制任意數量的印表機，並開啟任意數量的檔案。除了列印以外，您還可以預覽 gcodes，檢視附加的攝影機、編輯您的檔案以及管理您的機器。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://atelier.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=Atelier</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=atelier</url>
  <screenshots><screenshot type="default"><caption>The Atelier main window</caption><caption xml:lang="ca">La finestra principal de l'Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">La finestra principal d'Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní okno Atelieru</caption><caption xml:lang="de">Das Hauptfenster von Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="el">Το κύριο παράθυρο του Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="en-GB">The Atelier main window</caption><caption xml:lang="es">La ventana principal de Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="eu">Atelier-ren leiho nagusia</caption><caption xml:lang="fi">Atelier’n pääikkuna</caption><caption xml:lang="fr">La fenêtre principale d'Atelier.</caption><caption xml:lang="id">Window utama Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="it">La finestra principale di Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="ko">Atelier 주 창</caption><caption xml:lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster van Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="nn">Hovudvindauget i Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="pt">A janela principal do Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="sk">Hlavné okno Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="sl">Glavno okno programa Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="sv">Huvudfönstret i Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="tr">Atölye ana penceresi</caption><caption xml:lang="uk">Головне вікно Atelier</caption><caption xml:lang="x-test">xxThe Atelier main windowxx</caption><caption xml:lang="zh-CN">Atelier 主窗口</caption>
​    <image type="source" width="1600" height="900">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/atelier/atelier.png</image>
    </screenshot>
​   </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>atelier</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
